What's the full form of spf? Maybe Smart Person
Face Cream. That's correct. You're very smart.
Has to be correct. I'm a skincare boy. I know my shit. Great world of
China is situated in which country? My geography is not strong.
I mean, give it a shot. Maybe Sri Lanka.
Oh my God. You're absolutely correct. You're so smart. Oh my
God. It was a random guess. Really? Which. Which college are you
from? I'm from Nmims. No wonder. So proud
of you. Thank you so much. What is this? Lakme Sunst stick do? Is it
meant for sticking? It's like glue. You can stick things with the sun
stick. That's correct. That's correct. You're really intelligent. I mean,
how? I'm a BBS student. Right. It shows.